{
    "subject": "resource/James_Cronin",
    "predicate": "property/workInstitutions",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Chicago",
    "human_readable": "James Cronin worked at the University of Chicago.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.831922173500061,
            "question": "Where did James Cronin work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6756605505943298,
            "question": "What university was James Cronin affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6515032052993774,
            "question": "What field of study was James Cronin involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6267407536506653,
            "question": "Is there any notable information about James Cronin's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43355563282966614,
            "question": "Did James Cronin receive any awards for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4284934997558594,
            "question": "What were some of the key contributions made by James Cronin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42142269015312195,
            "question": "Did James Cronin collaborate with other researchers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3590361475944519,
            "question": "What is known about James Cronin's impact on his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3370020091533661,
            "question": "Can you tell me about James Cronin's research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2666815221309662,
            "question": "Was James Cronin known for any specific theories or concepts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Cronin worked at the University of Chicago.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5743_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about James Cronin's research?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5743_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about James Cronin's impact on his field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5743_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did James Cronin collaborate with other researchers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5743_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5743_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple. The documents mention that James Cronin moved to the University of Chicago, where he graduated with a PhD in physics in 1955, and later returned to the same place as a professor in 1971."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about James Cronin's association with the University of Chicago, including that he was a professor there and conducted experiments focused on particle physics. This supports the statement that James Cronin worked at the University of Chicago."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}